watch4.com 2019-12-10

# Start | Watch4

### Private Policy 

We look forward to your visit to our website watch4.com and your interest in our company and our offers. For external links to third-party content we accept no liability despite careful control of the content, as we have not initiated the transmission of this information, have not selected or changed the addressee of the information transmitted and the information transmitted itself. The protection of your personal data during the collection, processing and use during your visit to our website is important to us and takes place within the framework of the statutory provisions.)

In the following, we will explain what information we collect during your visit to our website and how it is used:

1\. Collection and storage of personal data as well as the nature and purpose of their use

a) When visiting the website  
Every time a customer (or other visitor) accesses our website, the internet browser used on your end device (computer, laptop, tablet, smartphone, etc.) automatically sends information to the server of our website. This information is temporarily stored in a so-called log file (log file).  
The following data will be collected without your intervention and stored until automated deletion:

\- IP address of the requesting computer, as well as device ID or individual device identifier and device type,  
\- the name of the retrieved file and the amount of data transferred, as well as the date and time of the retrieval,  
\- message about successful call,  
\- requesting domain,  
\- description of the type of internet browser used and, if applicable, the operating system of your terminal and the name of your access provider,  
\- Your browsing history and default weblog information, location data, including location data from your mobile device. Please note that for most mobile devices, you can control or disable the use of location services in the mobile device's settings menu.

Our legitimate interest in accordance. Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. f DSGVO for the collection of data is based on the following purposes:

\- ensuring a smooth connection setup and comfortable use of the website,  
\- Evaluation of system security and stability as well  
\- for further administrative purposes.

In no case we use the collected data for the purpose of drawing conclusions about you.

b) By using our contact form  
For questions of any kind, we offer you the opportunity to contact us via a form provided on the website. At least the indication of a valid e-mail address and your name is required so that we know from whom the request originates and in order to be able to answer them. Further information can be provided voluntarily.

The data processing for the purpose of contacting us is in accordance with. Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. a DSGVO based on your voluntarily granted consent.

The personal data collected by us for the use of the contact form will be automatically deleted after completion of the request made by you.

c) Upon conclusion of a contractual relationship

When concluding a contractual relationship on our website (eg registration on the website / platform), we ask you for the following personal data:

\- Data that personally identifies you, such as last name, first name and e-mail address  
\- the information about your means of payment  
\- other personal data that we are legally obliged or authorized to collect and process and that we need for your authentication, identification or verification of the data we collect.

The named data will be processed to process the contractual relationship. The processing of the data is based on Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b DSGVO. The storage period is limited to the purpose of the contract and, if available, statutory and contractual retention requirements.

d) Use of payment service providers  
For the execution of the contract, we also serve the following payment service providers. We provide your payment details in the context of the payment processing "earmarked to the payment". to the commissioned bank, if this is necessary for the payment transaction. The following payment service providers can be selected from us for payment.

Online Payments Group AG  
Sihleggstrasse 23  
8832 Wollerau  
mailto: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

PayPal Pte. Ltd.  
5 Temasek Boulevard  
# 09-01 Suntec Tower Five  
Singapore 038985

Commercial Register Number: 200509725E  
Authorized representative: Lawrence Chan.  
PayPal Pte. Ltd., based in Singapore, is regulated but not licensed by the Singapore tax authority.  
You can reach our customer service on 0800 721 133 (Mon-Fri 8:00 am to 9:30 pm and Sat-Sun 9:00 am to 7:30 pm) Free of charge from the Swiss fixed network Mobile networks may incur different charges depending on the network operator Call abroad, please dial 00353 1 436 90 81. Foreign costs may apply.). Please have your customer service PIN ready. You will see them immediately after logging in on the page \ "Contact \".

The legal basis for the transfer of data is Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b DSGVO.

e) When registering for our newsletter

If, pursuant to Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. a DSGVO have expressly consented, we will use your e-mail address to regularly send you our newsletter. The deregistration is possible at any time, for example via a link at the end of a newsletter. Alternatively, you can send your unsubscribe request at any time [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) email (preferably with the subject: 'unsubscribe newsletter').

2\. Disclosure of personal data

A transfer of your data to third parties for purposes other than those listed below does not take place.

We only share your information with third parties if:

\- you have given your express consent to this (Art. 6 (1) (1) (a) GDPR),  
\- this is necessary for the settlement of contractual relationships with you (Art. 6 (1) (b) GDPR),  
\- there is a legal obligation for disclosure (Art. 6 (1) (c) GDPR),  
\- disclosure is required to assert, exercise or defend legal claims and there is no reason to assume that you have an overriding interest in not disclosing your data (Art. 6 (1) sentence 1 lit. DSGVO).

In these cases, however, the amount of data transmitted is limited to the minimum required.

Our data protection regulations are in accordance with the applicable data protection regulations and the data are processed only in the Federal Republic of Germany and / or in Switzerland. That country was considered by the European Commission to be a third country ensuring an adequate level of data protection. In this respect, the European Commission has no reservations regarding the transfer of data to Switzerland and the transfer is possible on the basis of Art. 44 GDPR. More information can be found on the European Commission's website https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/adequacy-protection-personal-data-non -eu-countries_en. A transfer to other third countries does not take place and is not intended.

3\. Affected rights

a) Right to information

Upon request, we will gladly inform you whether and which personal data about you are stored (Art. 15 GDPR), in particular regarding the processing purposes, the category of personal data, the categories of recipients to whom your data has been disclosed, the planned retention period, the right of rectification, cancellation, limitation of processing or opposition, the existence of a right of appeal, the source of their data, if not collected by us, and the existence of automated decision-making including profiling.

b) Right to rectification

You also have the right to correct any incorrectly collected personal data or to complete incomplete data collected (Art. 16 GDPR).

c) Right to restriction of processing

Furthermore, you have the right to demand from us the restriction of the processing of your data, provided that the legal requirements for this exist (Art. 18 GDPR).

d) Data transferability

You have the right to receive the personal data relating to you in a structured, common and machine-readable format or to request the transfer to another person responsible (Art. 20 DSGVO).

e) Right to cancellation

In addition, you are entitled to the so-called "right to be forgotten", i. You can demand the deletion of your personal data from us, provided that the legal prerequisites exist for this (Art. 17 GDPR).

Regardless of this, your personal data will be automatically deleted by us if the purpose of the data collection has been omitted or the data processing has been unlawful.

f) Withdrawal

According to Art. 7 (3) GDPR, you have the right to revoke your once granted consent to us at any time. As a result, we are not allowed to continue the data processing based on this consent for the future.

You also have the right to object to the processing of your personal data at any time, provided that a right of objection is provided for by law. In the case of an effective cancellation, your personal data will also be automatically deleted by us (Article 21 GDPR).

If you would like to exercise your right of revocation or objection, please send an e-mail to: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

g) the right to complain

In case of violations of the data protection regulations you have acc. Art. 77 DSGVO the possibility to file a complaint with the competent supervisory authority.

4\. Duration of data storage  
The data collected will be stored by us as long as necessary for the performance of the contracts entered into with us or you have not exercised your right to cancellation or your right to transfer data to another company.

5\. Cookies and Cookie Policy

We use cookies on our website. These are small text files that your browser automatically creates and that are stored on your device when you visit our website.

In the cookie information is stored, each resulting in connection with the specific terminal used. However, this does not mean that we are immediately aware of your identity.

The use of cookies initially serves to make the use of our offer more pleasant for you: For example, we use so-called session cookies to recognize that you have already visited individual subpages of our website and, as long as you have registered Your password will be stored during the period of your visit to our website and the switching of sub-pages, so you will not have to re-enter it every time or your goods will be stored in the shopping cart until you 'checkout'. These session cookies are automatically deleted after leaving our website. In addition, to improve usability, we also use temporary cookies that are stored on your device for a specified period of time. If you visit our site again to take advantage of our services, it will automatically recognize that you have already been with us and what inputs and settings you have made in order not to have to re-enter them.

On the other hand, we use cookies to statistically record and evaluate the use of our website and to optimize our offer for you. These cookies enable us to automatically recognize when you visit our website again that you have already been with us. These cookies are automatically deleted after a defined time.

The data processed by cookies are for the purposes mentioned in order to safeguard our legitimate interests as well as third parties pursuant to Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. f DSGVO required. Most browsers accept cookies automatically. If you do not want us to recognize information about your computer, please set your internet browser to delete cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or warn you before a cookie is stored. You can find out how to delete or block cookies in the Help and Support section of your Internet browser. There you will find instructions for searching the file or directory where cookies are stored.

Please click here (

) for a complete list of cookies as well as an explanation of their function used on the Watch4 website.

Please note in any case that the complete deactivation of cookies may mean that you can not use all functions of our website.

If you come to our website via a link or clicking on any banner advertising or if you leave our website and thus access external pages, it may be that the addressees of the selected landing page also set cookies. We are not legally responsible for the cookies. For the use of such cookies and the information stored on them by our advertising partners, please compare their privacy policy and cookie policy.

Hi-Media Germany AG  
Emanuel-Leutze-Straße 8 | 40547 Dusseldorf - Germany  
www.hi-media.de/datenschutz-publisher/index.html

Goldbach Audience (Switzerland) AG  
SeestraSeestrasse 39 | 8700 Kusnacht  
http://www.goldbachaudience.ch/de-ch/datenschutz

netpoint media gmbh  
Rheinallee 60  
55283 Nierstein  
https://www.netpoint-media.de/technik/datenschutz

In providing our website Java Applets and Java Script are used. If you do not want to use these utilities or active content for security reasons, you should deactivate the corresponding setting of your browser.

6\. Online Marketing / Analysis Tools  
The tracking measures listed below and used by us are based on Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. f DSGVO, § 15 para. 3 TMG. With the tracking measures to be used, we want to ensure a needs-based design and the continuous optimization of our website. On the other hand, we use the tracking measures to statistically record the use of our website and evaluate it for the purpose of optimizing our offer for you. These interests are to be regarded as justified within the meaning of the aforementioned provision.

a) Google Analytics  
We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc, for the purpose of customizing and continually optimizing our web pages. https://www.google.com/ (1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA, hereafter 'Google'), in which context pseudonymised usage profiles are created and cookies are set (see above). The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website, such as browser type / version, operating system used, referrer URL (the previously visited page), host name of the accessing computer (IP address) and the time of the server request are sent to one Transfer server from Google in the US and store it there. The information is used to evaluate the use of the website, to compile reports on website activity and to provide other services related to website activity and internet usage for the purposes of market research and tailor-made website design. In these purposes, our legitimate interest lies in the data processing. The legal basis for the use of Google Analytics is Article 15 (3) TMG in conjunction with Article 6 (1) lit. f DSGVO.

This information may also be transferred to third parties if required by law or as far as third parties process this data in the order. Under no circumstances will your IP address be merged with any other data provided by Google. The IP addresses are anonymized, so that an assignment is not possible (so-called IP masking).

The data sent by us and linked with cookies, user IDs (eg user ID) or advertising IDs will be automatically deleted after 12 months. The deletion of data whose retention period has been reached is done automatically once a month.

For more information about Google Analytics Terms of Service and Privacy, please visit http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/en.html or http://www.google.com/intl/de/analytics/privacyoverview. html.

You can prevent the installation and storage of cookies by setting your browser software accordingly; However, we point out that in this case you may not be able to use all the features of this website in full.

In addition, you may prevent the collection of the data generated by the cookie and related to your use of the website (including your IP address) and the processing of this data by Google by downloading the browser plug-in available at the following link and install https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.

b) Google Adwords / Conversion Tracking

We also use the online advertising program "Google Ads". Google Ads Conversion Tracking. Google Conversion Tracking is a Google-provided analytics service.

When you click on an ad served by Google, a conversion tracking cookie will be placed on your device. These cookies lose their validity after 30 days, contain no personal data and are therefore not used for personal identification.

If you visit certain web pages on our website and the cookie has not expired, Google and we may recognize that you have clicked on the ad and have been redirected to this page. Each Google Ads customer receives a different cookie. Thus, there is no way that cookies can be tracked through Ads client websites.

The information gathered using the conversion cookie is used to generate conversion statistics for Ads customers who have opted for conversion tracking. It tells customers the total number of users who clicked on their ad and were redirected to a conversion tracking tag page. However, they do not receive any information that personally identifies users. In these purposes, our legitimate interest lies in the data processing. The legal basis for the use of Google Adwords / Conversion Tracking is § 15 para. 3 TMG in conjunction with Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f DSGVO.

If you do not want to participate in tracking, you can object to this use by preventing the installation of cookies from the domain 'googleadservices.com' by a corresponding setting of your browser software (deactivation option). You will not be included in the conversion tracking statistics. For more information and Google's privacy policy, please visit: http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/, http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.

c) Google Adsense  
This website uses Google AdSense, a service for integrating advertisements of Google Inc. ("Google"). Google AdSense uses "cookies", which are text files that are stored on your computer and that allow an analysis of the use of the website. Google AdSense also uses so-called web beacons (invisible graphics). These web beacons can be used to evaluate information such as visitor traffic on these pages.

The information generated by cookies and web beacons on the use of this website (including your IP address) and the delivery of advertising formats are transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the USA. This information may be shared by Google with Google's contractors. However, Google will not merge your IP address with other data you have stored.

You can prevent the installation of cookies by setting your browser software accordingly; However, please be aware that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

7\. Social Media Plugins  
On our website we use social media plugins of the following social networks.

Optional for Shariff solution: Here we use the so-called Shariff solution, which consists only of the linking of the corresponding social networks, so that a connection only arises, if you click on the button. After clicking the button and redirecting to the website of the social network, the obligation to inform is no longer with us, but with the operator of the social network.

a) Google Plus  
Our website uses the "+1" social button Google+ provided by Google. The Google+ plugin is indicated by the 'G +' sign. Clicking on the plugin will connect to the Google Plus servers. The content of the plugin is transmitted by Google directly to your browser and incorporated by him into the website. This redirects the information that you have visited our website to Google+.

We point out that as a provider of our website we have no knowledge of the content of the data transmitted and their use by Google+. According to Google, no personal data is collected without a click on the plugin. While you're logged in to the Google+ account, data, including the IP address, is collected and processed. If you want to prevent such data transmission, you must log out of your Google+ account before visiting our website.

The purpose and scope of the data collection and the further processing and use of the data by Google+, as well as your rights and settings options for protecting your privacy, can be found in the privacy notices of Google and Google+: https: //developers.google.com/+/web/buttons -policy.

b) Facebook  
Our website uses social plugins ("plugins") of the social network facebook.com, which is operated by Facebook Inc., 1 Hacker Way, Menlo Park, California 94025, USA ('Facebook'). If you open our website with the plugin, this connects directly to the servers of Facebook via your browser. This will transmit to Facebook the information that you have accessed the page.

If you are logged in with your Facebook account, by clicking on the plugin, the visit to our website can be assigned directly to your profile. Even if you do not have a profile, it can not be ruled out that your IP address will be saved by Facebook.

The purpose and scope of the data collection and the further processing and use of the data by Facebook, as well as your related rights and settings options to protect your privacy, please refer to the privacy policy (https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) of Facebook.

If you are a member of Facebook and do not want Facebook to collect data about you via our online offer and link it to your member data stored on Facebook, you must log out of our website on Facebook before visiting and delete corresponding Facebook cookies. It is also possible to block Facebook social plug-ins with add-ons for the browser, for example with the 'Facebook Blocker'.

c) Twitter  
On our website functions of the service Twitter are also included. These features are provided by Twitter Inc., Twitter, Inc. 1355 Market St., Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA. By using Twitter and the "Re-Tweet" feature, the web pages you visit will be linked to your Twitter account and shared with other users. This data is also transmitted to Twitter.

We point out that as a provider of our website we do not receive any knowledge of the content of the transmitted data and their use by Twitter. For more information, see the Twitter Privacy Policy at http://twitter.com/privacy. You can change your privacy settings on Twitter in the Account Settings at http://twitter.com/account/settings.

To prevent Twitter from collecting data when you visit our website, log out before visiting Twitter. To prevent general access from Twitter to your data via websites, you can exclude Twitter social plug-ins with an add-on for your browser (eg 'Twitter Blocker', https://disconnect.me).

8\. Data security  
We endeavor to provide all necessary technical and organizational security measures in order to store your personal data in such a way that they are neither accessible to third parties nor to the public. Should you wish to contact us by e-mail, we would like to point out that the confidentiality of the transmitted information can not be completely guaranteed with this communication channel. We therefore recommend that you send us confidential information only by post.

9\. Updating and changing this privacy policy  
This privacy statement is currently valid as of May 2018. As our website evolves and offers become available, or as a result of changes in legal or regulatory requirements, it may be necessary to change this privacy policy. The current privacy policy can be viewed and printed at any time on the website at watch4.com/privacy-statement.

10\. Name and contact details of the controller Article 4 (7) EU General Data Protection Regulation (DS-GVO)  
This privacy policy applies to data processing by:  
Responsible:

Video Solutions AG  
Industriestrasse 47  
CH-6300 Zug

Telephone: +41 41 76 31 643  
E-Mail: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
